Sean Lewis

Web Developer | London

Career Summary

I'm a self-taught developer, using online education resources including Treehouse, Udemy, and freeCodeCamp to learn and understand web development.

I've spent the last few months developing a strong practical understanding of some of the most widely used languages and frameworks. I'm also currently enrolled in the Code Institute Diploma in Full Stack Software Development, a part time course which will allow me to further develop my skills and abilities into the future.

I hope to continue to learn and improve as a developer while bringing the experience I've gained from my scientific background with me.

Education

Code Institute

Oct 2019 - Current

Diploma in Full Stack Software Development

Treehouse

May 2018 - Current

Front End Web Development React

Udemy

Aug 2019 - Current

The Web Developer Bootcamp
The Advanced Web Developer Bootcamp

Free Code Camp

Apr 2019 - Current

Responsive Web Design Javascript Algorithms & Data Structures

Trinity College Dublin

September 2010 - June 2014

BA in Microbiology (2.1)

Languages

HTML 5 CSS 3

Javascript (ES6)

Skills & Experience

User centric development Responsive web design Web optimization Web Accessibility Debugging

Bootstrap Node.js Express React AJAX Git HTTP

Key Competencies

Analytical thinking and problem solving

Ability to identify the root cause of problems and implement corrective and preventive actions.

Leadership and teamwork

Worked as part of select teams to complete large scale projects with an ability to drive results and maintain product quality. Led projects as senior analyst in MSD Brinny.

Adaptable and always willing to learn

Constantly learning new skills and improving current knowledge. Worked as a part of several multidisciplinary teams where it was necessary to develop cross-departmental understanding on the fly.

Experience

MSD Brinny

Senior Analyst

February 2018 - March 2019

Gained excellent teamwork and problem solving skills while working as a senior analyst.

Janssen Biologics

Analyst

May 2016 - February 2018

Gained experience in several disciplines working across a suite of quality control laboratories.

GlaxoSmithKline

Analyst

April 2015 - December 2015

Excelled as a laboratory technician where I gained valuable experience in the importance of maintaining work to the highest possible standards of quality.

Contact Details

Phone:

+44 7862 730 820

Email:

slewis100@gmail.com

Portfolio:

www.seanlewis.dev

GitHub:

www.github.com/SeanLewisIRE

Address: Sean Lewis, 157 Church Walk, Stoke Newington, London